[Music]
It was the night of July 15th and it was hot
An act of treason burned the country
Today is the day the whole nation stood up
Children and children, old and young, took to the streets
Shocked nation that democracy has been hit
Either freedom after this, or humiliation
The place trembled with the footsteps of millions
Flag in hand, takbir in tongue, ran forward
We are the witnesses in the saga of democracy
We are the martyrs who die one death and rise a thousand
The commander-in-chief gave the order: Get out!
Protect the flag, the beloved homeland!
We gave up, for the sake of homeland, nation and God!
The whole world was shocked to see this!
[Music]
From the ground, from the sky, while those traitors are dying
Many lives were martyred while raising the flag
Some stood up to the tank, some to the gun
So that democracy is never again
Democracy has suffered a blow, shame on the nation
Either freedom after this, or humiliation
The place trembled with the footsteps of millions
Flag in hand, takbir in tongue ran forward
We are the witnesses in the saga of democracy
We are the martyrs who die one death and rise a thousand
Commander-in-Chief gave the order; Get Out!
Protect the flag, the beloved homeland!
For the sake of our homeland, nation and God!
The whole world was shocked to see this!
[Music] Clap, clap, clap... He'He'Hey!
I wish our 251 martyrs mercy from Allah and my condolences to their places. Subtitle: EmirKaptan Admini